So, Greed's dead, then?
Yes, and in a certain way,
the way he died was just right for him.
Unsightly yet beautiful in its violence.
Well, even if one of us is lost,
you-know-who will just make another one.
Besides, we've located a new Wrath.
Right now, Sloth has him.
I wonder what we should
make him do...
What's wrong?
Don't tell me you're getting all sentimental over Greed dying.
Not really.
Something just crossed my mind.
Where do we come from, and where are we going?
What a load.
Patrons...
I'd like to close
the restaurant soon.
We're alive here, now....
Listen, sir...
...and we don't
need to go anywhere.
Isn't that enough for you?
Hey, are you listening to me?!
Shut up.
Can I eat him? Can I eat him?
Today, it's my treat.
Take your time.
Now that I think about it,
I've wondered about this before.
Where did I come from, and where am I going?
Stay with me!
Stay with me, Jimmy!
Excuse me!
Please let me through!
Please, let me
take a look at him.
He'll be all right now.
Thank you so much!
Lust...
Lujon...
Man cannot obtain anything
without first sacrificing something.
In order to obtain anything,
something of equal value is required.
That is alchemy's
Law of Equivalent Exchange.
At the time, we believed that
to be the true way of the world.
Brother, are you sure
this road is the right one?
We're definitely
heading south in any case.
We'll come upon the
Ishbalan camp before long.
I hope you're right.
But will you actually learn anything from asking the Ishbalans?
We don't have any other leads.
And I don't want to be manipulated by those homunculus guys.
Something the matter?
Just now...
I thought I heard
a woman scream...
Lujon!
Who the hell are you?!
For crying out loud... Here you are, springing up right on time...
What was that, you little runt?
Why, you!
It's been two years, hasn't it?
I never thought
I'd see you again.
I have so many things
I want to tell you.
But before that, I wonder
if you would tell me something.
Why did you disappear
from before me?
Why did you leave
without a word?
I don't remember.
It was so long ago.
I remember!
You taught me so many things!
Alchemy and something even more important.
What are you doing here?
You've never set foot outside of the village.
O-Oh, I'm looking
for a new Stone.
You remember, don't you?
Thanks to this Stone that you gave me,
our village was saved.
But that disease has
broken out again,
and this Stone's power
seems to have gotten weaker.
Please...
Will you lend me
your help again?
Once more,
like you did before.
A mudslide, huh?
This sure is quite a disaster.
Can I eat them? Can I eat them?
Stop doing that.
You should go on a bit of a diet.
Lucky girl, huh?
Here... Please...
Deliver these herbs to the village. Everyone is waiting for them.
Over there! There they are!
Hey, are you okay?!
Libia... Libia!
Stay with me, Libia!
I'm sorry, Lujon.
H-Here...
I told you not to do this!
This stuff won't
do us any good!
I'm surprised. You guys must've been riding in the carriage too, right?
Even so, you'd best get away
from here as soon as you can.
Fossilitis is spreading
throughout this whole area.
Fossilitis?
I'll cure it.
I'm going to
cure this with my...
with my alchemy.
So, you're traveling by yourself in order to find this man Lujon?
Yes.
I don't know what
your reasons are,
but it's really not good for a woman to be out alone.
Still...
I'm worried.
With the way things are going, I get the feeling that I'll never see Lujon again.
So, why did this Lujon guy leave your village?
He left to search for
a new Philosopher's Stone.
Philosopher's...
...Stone?!
Yes.
In order to cure the
fossilitis in our village,
he needs the power of the Stone,
no matter what.
It is a terrible disease,
which no medicine has any effect on.
Which is the reason why Lujon...
Here, drink this.
It will help you to relax.
Thanks.
From the looks of it, you weren't
hurt that badly, for which I'm glad.
L-Libia!
What's the matter?
Are you really hurt?
It's okay. My hand
just slipped a bit.
Lujon! Lujon, are you here?!
My son... My son...!
This is fossilitis.
The body suddenly begins changing into something like stone or dry wood.
People die, almost like
they are withering flowers.
Leave this boy, all that which is bringing calamity upon him.
Vasilisa, hear the cries of this boy.
Vasilisa, hear the grief of this boy.
Vasilisa, please accept this boy's prayer.
The enemy shall all be put to shame
and flee in terror.
They shall withdraw at once and be reproached.
I'm sorry.
Anji... Anji!
He had... He had only
just turned eight!
No!
I can't do anything!
All I can do is pray to God!
Vasilisa, my god,
I ask that with your power,
you please spare the little ones.
Please spare her!
Please, God...
Ishbala, my god...
I ask that with your power,
you would please
spare this little one.
Please spare them...
You're trying to use alchemy to
take the dead parts of the body
and reconstruct them back into a normal body, aren't you?
Now that medicine won't work,
you are not mistaken in your thinking.
However, you don't have
enough experience with alchemy.
I will teach you...
true alchemy.
I'm so happy.
Who would've thought that you'd ever come to our village again?
I told them that I left the village to
search for a new Philosopher's Stone,
but maybe I was
actually looking for you.
I wanted to see you again too.
I've had this feeling
for the longest time
that I left something
behind in the village.
Don't worry about it.
We're heading in the same direction anyway.
Thank you.
But I'm not really sure it's right
for me to go back to the village.
What choice do you have?
You may be out looking,
but you don't have any leads,
so there's not much else
you can do.
By any chance, is this Lujon-san fellow your boyfriend, or anything?
I...
was dumped by him.
I've been in love with him
for a long time.
But the one he is
really in love with is...
This is the place where you did your training, huh?
It does indeed look like you've at least got a lot of books together here.
What are you doing?!
Most of this is junk. First, you have to acquire the correct knowledge.
Read these in order.
Drill it all into your head.
It's no use.
This is too hard for me.
I just can't do this!
It's okay. You can do it.
You have the talent.
Come on, believe in yourself.
There it is again...
Who is that?
Why do I have these memories?
Yes, that's it.
What's this?
My gift to you. This Philosopher's Stone
will increase your power.
You can't start off with trying to heal people.
Try using your power to
return this bird to the skies.
May God save this creature
and watch over it, never slumbering.
The Lord is this creature's keeper; the sun shall not smite it by day,
nor the moon smite it by night.
I did it!
Like I told you,
you have the talent.
It's all because of you!
Thank you.
Could I ask you one more time?
Why did you disappear
from before me?
You knew how I felt
about you, didn't you?
You can't go looking
for all the answers.
It will end up
being your ruin.
I don't understand.
What are you trying to say?
Please, don't take Lujon...
Don't take Lujon away from me.
He and I are engaged.
Once my fossilitis is gone, we're getting married.
Isn't that nice?
Congratulations.
If you invite me to the ceremony, I'll give a speech.
Please don't joke around! I'm being serious!
Libia,
I will use my power
to heal you.
May God save this woman
and watch over her,
never slumbering.
The Lord is this woman's keeper;
the sun shall not
smite her by day,
nor the moon
smite her by night.
Incredible...
That's incredible, Lujon!
Cure my wife too!
Take care of my kid too!
You did it, Lujon!
How is it going?
Nothing to worry about.
Everything is proceeding right on schedule.
I'm counting on you.
After all, that's the whole reason why
we intentionally introduced this illness.
Lujon is starting to heal the disease with the fake Philosopher's Stone.
But that will only last
for the time being.
Next, I will take away
the power that I gave Lujon.
Then he will fall into
the depths of despair
and start seeking out
a genuine Philosopher's Stone.
And he'll be doing it for us.
We've been doing the same thing
all over the place,
all to find us a person who can create a genuine Philosopher's Stone.
Excuse me...
Oh, Libia, you're even
prettier than usual today.
Um, do you know
where Lujon is?
It's just about time for
the ceremony to start, isn't it?
I can't do it...
I can't go through with it.
Alchemy isn't the only thing that you taught me.
There's something
even more important.
I wonder what that could be.
I want you by my side forever.
Forever.
Who... Who are you?
You'd better go to her.
But...
Go!
Lust...
Hurry!
Libia!
Hey, are you sure about this?
I'm afraid of Envy.
We're nearly at the village.
Hang on, everyone.
With this new power...
Over here! Over here!
Hurry!
You've saved us again,
like you did two years ago.
Do you remember?
That day,
when I hugged you?
But this will be
different from then.
I won't let you go
this time.
Don't go!
Wh-Why?
You were my small...
blemish.
Where did I come from, and where am I going?
Lujon!
Lujon, where are you?!
Hey!
Libia-san!
This can't be...
Brother...
what in the world is this?
Hey... Hey...
Lust, I'm hungry. Hey...
Fullmetal Alchemist...
Episode 36: "The Sinner Within Us"
I think that anyone would be scared to see this mechanical arm.
Of course they would be.
However,
your heart isn't
necessarily always right.